A Guide to the Rockefeller Brothers Fund records, Projects (Grants), RG 3, Subgroup 1 and Subgroup 2 FA005
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Projects (Grants), 1947-1996; 3; 750 Cubic Feet
  - Projects (Grants), 1947-1989; 1
    - Food Research and Action Center, 1975-1976 (Box 343, Folder 2120)
    - For Responsive Media: Citizens Communication Center, 1971-1974 (Box 343, Folder 2121)
    - For Responsive Media: Citizens Communication Center, 1974 March-December (Box 343, Folder 2122)
    - For Responsive Media: Citizens Communication Center, 1975 (Box 343, Folder 2123)
    - For Responsive Media: Citizens Communication Center, 1976 (Box 344, Folder 2124)
    - For Responsive Media: Citizens Communication Center, Tax Information, 1974-1975 (Box 344, Folder 2125)
    - For Responsive Media: Citizens Communication Center, 1977 (Box 344, Folder 2126)
    - For Responsive Media: Citizens Communication Center, 1977-1980 (Box 344, Folder 2127)
    - Fordham University, Robert Moses Plaza, 1969 (Box 344, Folder 2128)
    - Foreign Policy Association (Foreign Policy Association and World Affairs Center for the United States merged 3/15/1960), 1947-1952 (Box 344, Folder 2129)
    - Foreign Policy Association, 1952-1955 (Box 344, Folder 2130)
    - Foreign Policy Association, 1955-1956 (Box 345, Folder 2131)
    - Foreign Policy Association, 1956 (Box 345, Folder 2132)
    - Foreign Policy Association, 1957 (Box 345, Folder 2133)
    - Foreign Policy Association, 1957-1958 (Box 345, Folder 2134)
    - Foreign Policy Association, 1958 (Box 345, Folder 2135)
    - Foreign Policy Association, 1959 (Box 346, Folder 2136)
    - Foreign Policy Association, 1960 (Box 346, Folder 2137)
    - Foreign Policy Association, 1961 January-March (Box 346, Folder 2138)
    - Foreign Policy Association, 1961-1962 (Box 346, Folder 2139)
    - Foreign Policy Association, 1963 January-December (Box 346, Folder 2140)
    - Foreign Policy Association, 1963-1964 (Box 347, Folder 2141)
    - Foreign Policy Association, 1965-1966 (Box 347, Folder 2142)
    - Foreign Policy Association, 1967-1969 (Box 347, Folder 2143)
    - Foreign Policy Association, 1970-1973 (Box 347, Folder 2144)
    - Foreign Policy Association, 1974 (Box 347, Folder 2145)
    - Foreign Policy Association, 1975 (Box 348, Folder 2146)
    - Foreign Policy Association, 1976-1982 (Box 348, Folder 2147)
    - Foreign Policy Association - Winslow Singer Study, 1954-1955 (Box 348, Folder 2148)
    - Fort Greene - Crown Heights Youth Service-Coalition, Inc. Tax Information, 1977 (Box 348, Folder 2149)
    - Fort Greene - Crown Heights Youth Service-Coalition, Inc. Tax Information, 1977-1980 (Box 348, Folder 2150)
    - (The) Fortune Society, 1968-1969 (Box 348, Folder 2151)
    - (The) Fortune Society, 1970-1973 (Box 348, Folder 2152)
    - (The) Fortune Society, Tax Information, 1972 (Box 349, Folder 2153)
    - 42nd Street Development Corporation, 1977-1978 (Box 349, Folder 2154)
    - 42nd Street Development Corporation, 1978-1979 (Box 349, Folder 2155)
    - 42nd Street Development Corporation, 1979 April-July (Box 349, Folder 2156)
    - 42nd Street Development Corporation, 1979 August-September (Box 349, Folder 2157)
    - 42nd Street Development Corporation, 1979 September-December (Box 349, Folder 2158)
    - 42nd Street Development Corporation, 1980-1981 (Box 350, Folder 2159)
    - 42nd Street Development Corporation, 1981-1983 (Box 350, Folder 2160)
    - 42nd Street Development Corporation, 1983 (Box 350, Folder 2161)
    - 42nd Street Development Corporation Tax Information, 1977-1983 (Box 350, Folder 2162)
    - 42nd Street Development Corporation, 1981-1986 (Box 350, Folder 2163)
    - 42nd Street Development Corporation Tax Information, 1981-1986 (Box 350, Folder 2164)
    - (The) Foundation Center, 1956-1966 (Box 350, Folder 2165)
      Formerly: The Foundation Library Center.
    - (The) Foundation Center, 1967-1968 (Box 351, Folder 2166)
    - (The) Foundation Center, 1969 January-May (Box 351, Folder 2167)
    - (The) Foundation Center, 1969 June-December (Box 351, Folder 2168)
    - (The) Foundation Center, 1970 (Box 351, Folder 2169)
    - (The) Foundation Center, 1971-1974 (Box 351, Folder 2170)
    - (The) Foundation Center, 1974-1975 (Box 352, Folder 2171)
    - (The) Foundation Center, 1976 (Box 352, Folder 2172)
    - (The) Foundation Center, 1977 (Box 352, Folder 2173)
    - (The) Foundation Center, 1978-1979 (Box 352, Folder 2174)
    - (The) Foundation Center, 1980 (Box 352, Folder 2175)
    - (The) Foundation Center, 1981-1982 (Box 353, Folder 2176)
    - (The) Foundation Center, Investment Study, 1962-1965 (Box 353, Folder 2177)
    - (The) Foundation Center, Investment Study, 1965-1969 (Box 353, Folder 2178)
    - (The) Foundation Center, Quarterly Reports, 1963-1969 (Box 353, Folder 2179)
    - (The) Foundation Center, Investment Study, 1970-1972 (Box 353, Folder 2180)
    - (The) Foundation Center, Last Quarter - Payments, 1972 (Box 354, Folder 2181)
    - (The) Foundation Center Reports - Payments, 1972 September-1973 (Box 354, Folder 2182)
    - (The) Foundation Center Reports - Payments, 1973 (Box 354, Folder 2183)
    - (The) Foundation Center Reports, 1974 January-September (Box 354, Folder 2184)
    - (The) Foundation Center Reports, 1974 September-1975 (Box 354, Folder 2185)
    - (The) Foundation Center Reports, 1975 (Box 354, Folder 2186)
    - (The) Foundation Center Reports, 1976-1977 (Box 355, Folder 2187)
    - (The) Foundation Center Reports, 1977 (Box 355, Folder 2188)
    - (The) Foundation Center Reports, 1978 (Box 355, Folder 2189)
    - (The) Foundation Center Reports, 1978-1979 (Box 355, Folder 2190)
    - (The) Foundation Center - YA Distribution Copies Of Paper "Visiting Committees for Evaluation", 1968 (Box 355, Folder 2191)
    - Foundation for American Dance Inc., 1966-1967 (Box 355, Folder 2192)
    - Foundation for American Dance Inc. Tax Information, 1971-1972 (Box 355, Folder 2193)
    - Foundation for American Dance Inc., 1970-1974 (Box 356, Folder 2194)
    - (The) Foundation for Art Education, 1976-1977 (Box 356, Folder 2195)
    - (The) Foundation for Art Education, Tax File, 1977-1981 (Box 356, Folder 2196)
    - (The) Foundation for Art Education, 1977-1981 (Box 356, Folder 2197)
    - Foundation for P.R.I.D.E. - Turks and Caicos-Development Trust, 1981 July 22 (Box 356, Folder 2198)
    - Foundation for P.R.I.D.E. - Turks and Caicos-Development Trust, 1981 July 22 (Box 356, Folder 2199)
    - Foundation for Research of the New York-Academy of Osteopathy, Inc., 1960-1961 (Box 357, Folder 2200)
    - Foundation for Research of the New York-Academy of Osteopathy, Inc., 1962-1963 (Box 357, Folder 2201)
    - Foundation for Research of the New York-Academy of Osteopathy, Inc., 1963-1964 (Box 357, Folder 2202)
    - Foundation for Research of the New York-Academy of Osteopathy, Inc., 1965-1967 (Box 357, Folder 2203)
    - Foundation for the Graduate Institute of-International Studies, 1966-1967 (Box 357, Folder 2204)
    - Foundation for the Joffrey Ballet, Inc. Tax Information, 1976-1982 (Box 357, Folder 2205)
    - Foundation for the Joffrey Ballet, Inc., 1980-1983 (Box 358, Folder 2206)
    - Foundation for the Open Eye, Inc. Tax Information, 1977 (Box 358, Folder 2207)
    - Foundation for the Open Eye, Inc., 1977-1980 (Box 358, Folder 2208)
    - Fountain House Foundation, Inc., 1950-1955 (Box 358, Folder 2209)
    - Fountain House Foundation, Inc., 1956-1959 (Box 358, Folder 2210)
    - Fountain House Foundation, Inc., 1959-1965 (Box 358, Folder 2211)
    - Fountain House Foundation, Inc., 1966-1968 (Box 359, Folder 2212)
    - Fountain House Foundation, Inc., 1970-1973 (Box 359, Folder 2213)
    - Fountain House Foundation, Inc. Tax Information, 1970-1973 (Box 359, Folder 2214)
    - Fountain House Foundation, Inc., 1973-1976 (Box 359, Folder 2215)
    - Four Freedom Foundation, 1972-1980 (Box 359, Folder 2216)
    - 14th Street - Union Square Area Project Tax Information, 1978-1979 (Box 359, Folder 2217)
    - 14th Street - Union Square Area Project, 1978-1982 (Box 359, Folder 2218)
    - Franklin Book Programs, Inc. (Formerly: Franklin Publications), 1961-1964 (Box 359, Folder 2219)
    - Franklin Book Programs, Inc., 1964-1965 (Box 360, Folder 2220)
    - Franklin Book Programs, Inc., 1965-1970 (Box 360, Folder 2221)
    - Franklin Book Programs, Inc., 1970 (Box 360, Folder 2222)
    - (The) Franklin Institute, 1963-1969 (Box 360, Folder 2223)
    - (The) Franklin Institute, 1971-1976 (Box 360, Folder 2224)
    - (The) Franklin Institute, 1976-1977 (Box 360, Folder 2225)
    - (The) Franklin Institute, Tax Information, 1976 (Box 361, Folder 2226)
    - Frederick Burk Foundation for Education, 1971-1973 (Box 361, Folder 2227)
    - Frederick Burk Foundation for Education, 1974-1975 (Box 361, Folder 2228)
    - Frederick Burk Foundation for Education Tax Information, 1973-1974 (Box 361, Folder 2229)
    - Frederick Douglass Museum of African Art, 1964-1966 (Box 361, Folder 2230)
    - Frederick Douglass Museum of African Art, 1968 (Box 361, Folder 2231)
    - Frederick Douglass Museum of African Art, 1968-1969 (Box 361, Folder 2232)
      50 colored slides relocated to Rockefeller Brothers Fund photograhs box 1495
    - Frederick Douglass Museum of African Art Tax Information, 1977-1980 (Box 362, Folder 2233)
    - Frederick Douglass Museum of African Art, 1970-1980 (Box 362, Folder 2234)
    - Free Southern Theater, Inc., 1967-1969 (Box 362, Folder 2235)
    - Free Southern Theater, Inc., 1970-1972 (Box 362, Folder 2236)
    - Free Southern Theater, Inc., 1972-1973 (Box 362, Folder 2237)
    - Free Southern Theater, Inc. Tax Information, 1970-1973 (Box 362, Folder 2238)
    - (The) Fresh Air Fund (Formerly: Herald Tribune Fresh Air Fund), 1952-1959 (Box 362, Folder 2239)
    - (The) Fresh Air Fund, 1959-1964 (Box 362, Folder 2240)
    - (The) Fresh Air Fund, 1964-1969 (Box 363, Folder 2241)
    - (The) Fresh Air Fund, 1970-1976 (Box 363, Folder 2242)
    - The) Fresh Air Fund, 1977-1978 (Box 363, Folder 2243)
    - The) Fresh Air Fund, Tax Information, 1971-1975 (Box 363, Folder 2244)
    - Friendly Homes, Inc., 1968-1969 (Box 363, Folder 2245)
    - Friendly Homes, Inc. Tax Information, 1970 (Box 363, Folder 2246)
    - Friendly Homes, Inc., 1970-1971 (Box 363, Folder 2247)
    - Friends of Women's World Banking/USA, Inc., 1980-1982 (Box 363, Folder 2248)
    - (The) Friendship Force, 1976-1978 (Box 364, Folder 2249)
    - (The) Friendship Force, 1978 (Box 364, Folder 2250)
    - (The) Friendship Force, 1979 January-February (Box 364, Folder 2251)
    - (The) Friendship Force, 1979 (Box 364, Folder 2252)
    - (The) Friendship Force, 1980-1982 (Box 365, Folder 2253)
    - (The) Fund for Area Planning and Development, Inc. (Formerly: East River - Turtle Bay Fund Inc.), 1966-1969 (Box 365, Folder 2254)
    - (The) Fund for Area Planning and Development, Inc., 1968 (Box 366, Folder 2255)
    - Fund for Multinational Management Education, 1977-1982 (Box 367, Folder 2256)
    - Fund for Multinational Management Education, 1982 (Box 367, Folder 2257)
    - Fund for Multinational Management Education, 1982 October-December (Box 367, Folder 2258)
    - Fund for Multinational Management Education, 1983 January-March (Box 367, Folder 2259)
    - Fund for Multinational Management Education, 1983 March-November (Box 368, Folder 2260)
    - Fund for Multinational Management Education, 1984 February-May (Box 368, Folder 2261)
    - Fund for Multinational Management Education, 1984-1985 (Box 368, Folder 2262)
    - Fund for Multinational Management Education, 1985-1986 (Box 368, Folder 2263)
    - Fund for Multinational Management Education, 1986 (Box 368, Folder 2264)
    - Fund for Peaceful Atomic Development, Inc., 1955 January-April (Box 369, Folder 2265)
    - Fund for Peaceful Atomic Development, Inc., 1955 April-October (Box 369, Folder 2266)
    - Fund for Peaceful Atomic Development, Inc., 1955-1956 (Box 369, Folder 2267)
    - Fund for Peaceful Atomic Development, Inc., 1956-1962 (Box 369, Folder 2268)
    - Fund for the City of New York, Inc., 1974-1976 (Box 369, Folder 2269)
    - Fund for the City of New York, Inc., 1977-1982 (Box 369, Folder 2270)
    - (The) Fund for Theological Education, Inc., 1952-1953 (Box 370, Folder 2271)
    - (The) Fund for Theological Education, Inc., 1954 (Box 370, Folder 2272)
    - (The) Fund for Theological Education, Inc., 1954 May-December (Box 370, Folder 2273)
    - (The) Fund for Theological Education, Inc., 1955 (Box 370, Folder 2274)
    - (The) Fund for Theological Education, Inc., 1955-1956 (Box 371, Folder 2275)
    - (The) Fund for Theological Education, Inc., 1957-1958 (Box 371, Folder 2276)
    - (The) Fund for Theological Education, Inc., 1959 (Box 371, Folder 2277)
    - (The) Fund for Theological Education, Inc., 1960-1961 (Box 371, Folder 2278)
    - (The) Fund for Theological Education, Inc., 1962 (Box 372, Folder 2279)
    - (The) Fund for Theological Education, Inc., 1963 (Box 372, Folder 2280)
    - (The) Fund for Theological Education, Inc., 1964 (Box 372, Folder 2281)
    - (The) Fund for Theological Education, Inc., 1965 January-June (Box 372, Folder 2282)
    - (The) Fund for Theological Education, Inc., 1965 July-December (Box 372, Folder 2283)
    - (The) Fund for Theological Education, Inc., 1966 January-May (Box 373, Folder 2284)
    - (The) Fund for Theological Education, Inc., 1966 May-December (Box 373, Folder 2285)
    - (The) Fund for Theological Education, Inc., 1967 January-May (Box 373, Folder 2286)
    - (The) Fund for Theological Education, Inc., 1967 May-December (Box 373, Folder 2287)
    - (The) Fund for Theological Education, Inc., 1968 January-May (Box 373, Folder 2288)
    - (The) Fund for Theological Education, Inc., 1968 June-December (Box 374, Folder 2289)
    - (The) Fund for Theological Education, Inc., 1969 (Box 374, Folder 2290)
    - (The) Fund for Theological Education, Inc., 1970 (Box 374, Folder 2291)
    - (The) Fund for Theological Education, Inc., 1971 January-May (Box 374, Folder 2292)
    - (The) Fund for Theological Education, Inc., 1971 May-September (Box 374, Folder 2293)
    - (The) Fund for Theological Education, Inc., 1971 September-December (Box 375, Folder 2294)
    - (The) Fund for Theological Education, Inc., 1971-1972 (Box 375, Folder 2295)
    - (The) Fund for Theological Education, Inc., 1972-1973 (Box 375, Folder 2296)
    - (The) Fund for Theological Education, Inc., 1973 June-August (Box 375, Folder 2297)
    - (The) Fund for Theological Education, Inc., 1974 January-April (Box 375, Folder 2298)
    - (The) Fund for Theological Education, Inc., 1974-1975 (Box 376, Folder 2299)
    - (The) Fund for Theological Education, Inc., 1974-1976 (Box 376, Folder 2300)
    - (The) Fund for Theological Education, Inc., 1976 March-November (Box 376, Folder 2301)
    - (The) Fund for Theological Education, Inc. Letters of Gratitude to York Allen, 1976 February-April (Box 376, Folder 2302)
    - (The) Fund for Theological Education, Inc. Letters of Gratitude to York Allen, 1976 April-June (Box 376, Folder 2303)
    - (The) Fund for Theological Education, Inc., 1977-1978 (Box 377, Folder 2304)
    - (The) Fund for Theological Education, Inc., 1978-1982 (Box 377, Folder 2305)
    - (The) Fund for Theological Education, Inc., 1962-1964 (Box 377, Folder 2306)
    - (The) Fund for Theological Education, Inc. Rockefeller Doctoral Fellowship in Religion Program, 1973-1976 (Box 377, Folder 2307)
    - Fundacion Luis Munoz Marin, Inc., 1981-1982 (Box 377, Folder 2308)
    - Fundacion Nicaraguense De Desarrollo, 1973 (Box 377, Folder 2309)
    - Fundacion Nicaraguense De Desarrollo, 1973-1974 (Box 378, Folder 2310)
    - Fundacion Nicaraquense De Desarrollo, 1975 (Box 378, Folder 2311)
    - Fundacion Nicaraquense De Desarrollo, 1975-1976 (Box 378, Folder 2312)
    - Fundacion Nicaraquense De Desarrollo, Tax Information, 1964-1976 (Box 378, Folder 2313)
    - Fundacion Nicaraquense De Desarrollo, 1977-1983 (Box 378, Folder 2314)
    - Growth Through Art and-Museum Experience, Inc.(GAME), 1973-1975 (Box 378, Folder 2315)
      2 photographs relocated to Rockefeller Brothers Fund photographs box 1496
    - Growth Through Art and-Museum Experience, Inc. (GAME), 1975-1976 (Box 378, Folder 2316)
    - Growth Through Art and-Museum Experience, Inc. (GAME), 1975-1976 (Box 379, Folder 2317)
    - Growth Through Art and-Museum Experience, Inc. (GAME), 1975-1976 (Box 379, Folder 2318)
    - Growth Through Art and-Museum Experience, Inc. (GAME), 1975-1976 (Box 379, Folder 2319)
    - Garoua School for the Training of Wildlife Specialist, 1970-1971 (Box 379, Folder 2320)
      4 photographs and negatives relocated to Rockefeller Brothers Fund photographs box 1495
      For material prior to 10/70 see: African Wildlife-Leadership Foundation Garoua
    - Garoua School for the Training of Wildlife Specialist, 1971-1972 (Box 379, Folder 2321)
    - Garoua School for the Training of Wildlife Specialist, 1972 April-November (Box 379, Folder 2322)
    - Garoua School for the Training of Wildlife Specialist, 1973 (Box 380, Folder 2323)
      4 photographs relocated to Rockefeller Brothers Fund photographs box 1496
    - Garoua School for the Training of Wildlife Specialist, 1974-1975 (Box 380, Folder 2324)
    - Garoua School for the Training of Wildlife Specialist, 1975-1976 (Box 380, Folder 2325)
    - Garoua School for the Training of Wildlife Specialist-Tax Information, 1971-1976 (Box 380, Folder 2326)
    - Garoua School for the Training of Wildlife Specialist, 1977-1980 (Box 380, Folder 2327)
      1 photograph 1 letter relocated to Rockefeller Brothers Fund photographs box 1496
    - George C. Marshall Research Foundation, 1960-1970 (Box 381, Folder 2328)
      14 photographs relocated to Rockefeller Brothers Fund photographs box 1496
    - George C. Marshall Research Foundation, 1970-1976 (Box 381, Folder 2329)
    - Georgetown University, 1977-1982 (Box 381, Folder 2330)
    - Georgetown University, 1983 January-August (Box 381, Folder 2331)
    - Georgetown University, 1983 August-December (Box 381, Folder 2332)
    - George Washington University-Center for Museum Education, 1974-1976 (Box 381, Folder 2333)
      3 photographs relocated to Rockefeller Brothers Fund photographs box 1496
    - George Washington University-Center for Museum Education, 1977 (Box 382, Folder 2334)
    - George Washington University-Center for Museum Education, Tax Information, 1976-1982 (Box 382, Folder 2335)
    - George Washington University-Center for Museum Education, 1978 (Box 382, Folder 2336)
    - George Washington University-Center for Museum Education, 1979-1982 (Box 382, Folder 2337)
    - Georgia Council on Human Relations, 1957-1968 (Box 382, Folder 2338)
    - Georgia Council on Human Relations, 1970-1973 (Box 382, Folder 2339)
    - Georgia Council on Human Relations, 1973-1974 (Box 382, Folder 2340)
    - Georgia Council on Human Relations, Tax Information, 1971-1974 (Box 383, Folder 2341)
    - Georgia Council on Human Relations, 1975-1976 (Box 383, Folder 2342)
    - Girl Scout Council of Greater New York, Inc., 1941-1949 (Box 383, Folder 2343)
    - Girl Scout Council of Greater New York, Inc., 1949-1956 (Box 383, Folder 2344)
      21 photographs relocated to Rockefeller Brothers Fund photographs box 1496
    - Girl Scout Council of Greater New York, Inc., 1956-1966 (Box 383, Folder 2345)
    - Girl Scout Council of Greater New York, Inc., 1966-1971 (Box 383, Folder 2346)
    - Girl Scout Council of Greater New York, Inc., 1971-1976 (Box 384, Folder 2347)
    - Girl Scout Council of Greater New York, Inc. Tax Information, 1970-1977 (Box 384, Folder 2348)
    - Girl Scout Council of Greater New York, Inc., 1977 (Box 384, Folder 2349)
    - Girl Scout Council of Greater New York, Inc., 1977-1981 (Box 384, Folder 2350)
    - Girl Scouts of America-Abnaki Council Tax Information, 1972-1973 (Box 384, Folder 2351)
    - Girl Scouts of America-Abnaki Council, 1972-1979 (Box 384, Folder 2352)
    - (The) Girls' Scout of Manhattan, Inc. Tax Information, 1970-1972 (Box 384, Folder 2353)
    - (The) Girls' Scout of Manhattan, Inc., 1970-1972 (Box 384, Folder 2354)
    - (The) Girls' Club of New York City, Inc. Tax Information, 1980-1982 (Box 384, Folder 2355)
    - (The) Girls' Club of New York City, Inc., 1979-1982 (Box 385, Folder 2356)
    - Girls Clubs of America, Inc., 1948-1964 (Box 385, Folder 2357)
    - Girls Clubs of America, Inc., 1964-1965 (Box 385, Folder 2358)
    - Girls Clubs of America, Inc., 1965-1969 (Box 385, Folder 2359)
    - Girls Clubs of America, Inc., 1970-1978 (Box 385, Folder 2360)
    - Global Tomorrow Coalition, 1982-1985 (Box 385, Folder 2361)
    - Global Tomorrow Coalition, 1985 (Box 386, Folder 2362)
    - Global Tomorrow Coalition, 1985-1986 (Box 386, Folder 2363)
    - Global Tomorrow Coalition, 1986 (Box 386, Folder 2364)
    - Goodard-Riverside Community Center, 1962-1966 (Box 386, Folder 2365)
    - Goodard-Riverside Community Center, 1966-1969 (Box 386, Folder 2366)
    - Goethe Bicentennial Foundation, 1949 (Box 386, Folder 2367)
    - Good Hope School (Virgin Island) Tax Information, 1976-1980 (Box 386, Folder 2368)
    - Good Hope School (Virgin Island), 1975-1977 (Box 387, Folder 2369)
    - Good Hope School (Virgin Island), 1978 (Box 387, Folder 2370)
    - Good Hope School (Virgin Island), 1978-1982 (Box 387, Folder 2371)
    - Grace Congregational Church Center, 1968-1969 (Box 387, Folder 2372)
    - Grace United Methodist Church, Tax Information, 1979 (Box 387, Folder 2373)
    - Grace United Methodist Church (Brooklyn), 1979-1980 (Box 387, Folder 2374)
    - Grace United Methodist Church (Brooklyn), 1980-1982 (Box 387, Folder 2375)
    - Graduate Theological Union, 1972-1974 (Box 388, Folder 2376)
    - Graduate Theological Union, 1974-1975 (Box 388, Folder 2377)
    - Graduate Theological Union, 1975 January-July (Box 388, Folder 2378)
    - Graduate Theological Union, 1975 September-December (Box 388, Folder 2379)
    - Graduate Theological Union, 1976 January-June (Box 388, Folder 2380)
    - Graduate Theological Union, 1976 July-December (Box 389, Folder 2381)
    - Graduate Theological Union, Tax Information, 1974-1977 (Box 389, Folder 2382)
    - Graduate Theological Union, 1977-1980 (Box 389, Folder 2383)
    - Graham-Windham, Tax Information; (Formerly: Orphan Asylum Society in the City of New York, -Graham Home for Children), 1970-1975 (Box 389, Folder 2384)
    - Graham-Windham, 1970-1976 (Box 389, Folder 2385)
    - Graham-Windham, 1977-1981 (Box 389, Folder 2386)
    - Graham-Windham - Handbook for a Case Management-System in a Residential Treatment Setting (Box 389, Folder 2387)
    - Greater Cleveland Teacher Center for Informal Education Tax Information, 1974-1975 (Box 389, Folder 2388)
    - Greater Cleveland Teacher Center for Informal Education, 1974 (Box 390, Folder 2389)
    - Greater Cleveland Teacher Center for Informal Education, 1974-1978 (Box 390, Folder 2390)
    - Greater Jamaica Development Corporation, 1973-1974 (Box 390, Folder 2391)
    - Greater Jamaica Development Corporation, 1974-1980 (Box 390, Folder 2392)
    - Greater Jamaica Development Corporation - Tax Information, 1973-1977 (Box 390, Folder 2393)
    - Greater New York Council for Foreign Students, 1953 February-June (Box 390, Folder 2394)
    - Greater New York Council for Foreign Students, 1953 June-December (Box 390, Folder 2395)
    - Greater New York Council for Foreign Students, 1954-1955 (Box 391, Folder 2396)
    - Greater New York Council for Foreign Students, 1955-1958 (Box 391, Folder 2397)
    - Greater New York Council for Foreign Students, 1958-1966 (Box 391, Folder 2398)
    - Greater New York Federation of Churches, 1941-1946 (Box 391, Folder 2399)
    - (The) Greater New York Fund, Inc., 1957-1965 (Box 391, Folder 2400)